# Danielle Parra

# **Network Engineer**

United States danielleparra1983@yahoo.com (213) 999-0511

Extensive customer service experience; proven customer service and problem-solving skills, working face-to-face and on-site with customers, providing technical support for a full range of business technology, including computer systems (hardware and software), network infrastructure, telecommunications circuits, mobile devices, telephone systems, and audio-visual equipment. Seasoned in independently assessing a reported problem or failure using diagnostic methods and tools, determine the likely cause and take appropriate action to resolve the problem in a timely manner. Collaborates well with other resources (both internal and external), while understanding system interdependencies and aimed at preventing unintentional interruption of services during troubleshooting and problem resolution.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

## **Network Engineer**

William Hill US - Las Vegas, NV September 2020 to Present

- Provide "smart hands" assistance to include rebooting equipment, reseating line cards, and providing equipment status information to remote technicians.
- Perform special customer requests in accordance with their respective SLA's; Rack and stack any networking equipment in various data centers throughout the United States.
- Ability to read, interpret, and understand structured cable design diagrams; Understanding of EIA/TIA structured cabling standards.
- Basic understanding of network fundamentals, LAN switching technologies, routing technologies, network infrastructure services (DNS, DHCP), and network infrastructure maintenance.
- Working knowledge and experience with networking components (routers, switches, access points).
- Knowledge of layer-3 routing protocols (HSRP, OSPF, ICMP).
- Basic network troubleshooting and problem-solving.
- Network device configuration from command-line and graphical interfaces.
- Experience configuring HP DL160s servers with VMware

#### **DESKTOP SUPPORT ADMINISTRATOR**

WILLIAM HILL SPORTSBOOK - Las Vegas, NV August 2017 to September 2020

#### **INFOSEC**

- Manage the SOC mailbox, monitor and analyze emails for threats including phishing, malware, and escalate per procedure.
- Escalate alerts that require analysis to Level 2 SOC analysts.

• Participate in Investigations of security violations, breaches and prepare reports on intrusions as needed.

#### **DESKTOP SUPPORT**

- Configure VoIP phones for new users and new sportsbooks.
- Configure wireless phones, Cisco/Polycom devices and programs for use in conference and boardrooms.
- Order stock when necessary and ship hardware to various sportsbooks throughout the US.
- Keep track of inventory, update and maintain Asset Manager.
- Provide level 2 support to William Hill Sportsbooks in NV, MS, IA, IN, NJ, PA, and FL.

#### SUPPORT SPECIALIST

CAESAR'S ENTERTAINMENT June 2015 to July 2017

- Responsible for supervising the installation of computers, computer-related equipment and all components.
- Assisted in setting up all PC's, printers, scanners and POS Terminals (Hardware and Software).
- Utilized tools such as Windows Backup Utility and Windows ADK to backup and restore files or operating systems.
- Created bootable flash drives for POS upgrades.
- Maintain and troubleshoot, printers, fax machines, and other office equipment.

#### **HELP DESK TECHNICIAN**

COMPUTEL ON-DEMAND

November 2012 to June 2017

- Provided first level support to clients on hardware and software related issues.
- Tested software and hardware to evaluate appropriateness and ease of use for user.
- Followed up with customers to ensure that the expected services were completed.
- Monitored the status of a problem and followed-up on unresolved issues.
- Consulted with Tier 2 and Tier 3 technicians to research problems and find solutions.
- Worked with a team pulling CAT 5E and CAT 6 cable from server rooms to all rooms within new offices and activated jacks on the patch panel.

## Education

### **CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMENT in Network and Security Management**

WEST LOS ANGELES COLLEGE - Los Angeles, CA

January 2016 to March 2016

## **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE in Information Systems Security**

WESTWOOD COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

2006

#### Skills

Working knowledge of TCP/IP networking protocol.

- Use Diagnostic Techniques, tools, and utilities to troubleshoot network problems.
- Analyze problems, research potential solutions, isolate issues, and refer complex problems to senior technical staff.
- Active Directory
- LAN
- Help Desk
- Network Support
- DNS
- Microsoft Windows
- Technical Support
- Microsoft Windows Server
- Operating Systems
- Information Security
- Network Firewalls
- · Network Monitoring
- DHCP
- WAN
- · Network protocols
- Computer networking
- System security
- Encryption
- Network Infrastructure
- MPLS
- VPN
- VoIP
- Data center experience
- System Administration
- Network Engineering
- Network Administration
- FTP
- · Load Balancing
- Authentication
- VMWare (1 year)
- EIGRP
- BGP
- ServiceNow (4 years)
- OSPF
- Ethernet
- Remote Access Software
- IT support (10+ years)

# Certifications and Licenses

CompTIA A+ January 2020 to January 2023

# CompTIA Network+

January 2020 to January 2023

# CCNA